好的，我知道了。你们实际上想要
All right, I get the hint. You actually want
这个课程能在下一个版本的Android
this class to be finished sometime before the next
出来前结束。就快结束了。我们看看
Android release happens. We're almost done. So we look
ForecastFragment里的onStart函数。我们其实耍了点小聪明
in ForecastFragment in onStart. We've actually been cheating a
每一次我们执行onStart的时候
bit. Every single time we get to onStart, we
我们其实也更新了天气。我们删掉这一行
actually update the weather. Let's get rid of that.
这会迫使我们不得不用
It'll force us to actually have to use the
refresh函数来获得新的天气，但是这也会帮助说明
refresh function to get new weather, but it'll help illustrate
一样很酷的东西关于我们即将用到的preference
the cool stuff we're about to do with preferences.
我们不耍小聪明了。在onPreferenceChange里，如果
We're going to stop cheating here. In onPreferenceChange, if we're
我们还没有设置偏好，如果地址改变，我们将执行一个新的
not actually binding preferences, we're going to execute a new
FetchWeatherTask。否则，我们就
FetchWeatherTask if there's a change in location. Otherwise, we'll just
通知CONTENT_URI来允许光标的信息更新。
notify our CONTENT_URI to allow our cursor to update.
我们还要再做一件事。在ForecastFragment里
We still have to do one more thing. In ForecastFragment
我们用了一个实例变量（mLocation）来储存
we've been using an instance variable, mLocation, to save the
我们从onCreateLoader里获得的偏好地址
preferred location we get when we're actually an onCreateLoader.
我们这样做是因为我们计划
We've been doing that because we've been planning to
使用这个数据一段时间。接下来我们要覆盖另一个函数。
use this for a while. Let's override another function. In
在onResume里，我们需要检查
onResume we need to check to see whether or not
地址是不是改变了。所以如果地址
our location has changed. So if our location is not
不等于null并且Utility.getPreferredLocation和mLocation
equal to null and Utility.getPreferredLocation does not equal
不一致，这时候我们就可以调用更新天气的函数。我们看看
location, well, then we can call update weather. Let's see
发生什么了。你能看到它立刻就变回去了。你看
what happens. You see it immediately changed back. You didn't
不到载入过程因为它不需要载入任何东西。
see that loading because it didn't have to load anything.
但是，如果我们把设置改成其他的地址
However, if we change settings to something else,
它在后台刷新数据。从这里能看到
it's refreshing in the background. Well, it turns out
这里的updateWeather并没有帮到我们。为什么呢？
updating weather doesn't actually help us here. Why?
因为我们的URI没有变。记住，我们做的
Because our URI hasn't changed. Remember, we're doing
所有东西都是基于URI的。我们真正需要
everything based upon URI. What we really need
做的是重置载入程序
to do is reset our loader. So, how
要怎样做呢？这个非常简单
do we do that? Well, it's pretty straightforward.
就像我们在onActivityCreated里做的一样。我们
Just like we did in onActivityCreated, we have to
不得不使用LoaderManager。所以不需要调用updateWeather
use LoaderManager. So instead of calling updateWeather, what
真正要做的是调用其他的一些函数
we're actually going to do is call something else.
这种情况，不是调用initLoader，而是调用restartLoader
In this case, not an initLoader, but restartLoader.
它和initLoader需要一样的参数。
It takes the same parameters as an initLoader. Now
我们再来试试。看起来好多了
let's try this again. That already looks better.
好了，我们换回我们自己的天气吧
All right, let's change back to our own weather
这就是了。你能看到
again. And there we are. As you can see,
当地址改变时天气也改变了
the weather is changing as we go from location
但是我们还是有这个问题
to location, but we still have this
明显的，当我们在这里更改设置时
problem. Obviously when we change settings here,
没有任何作用。我们需要修复这个。那就是你们要做的了。
it doesn't affect anything, so we need to fix that. That's where you come in.